{
    "id": "0e776b21c18e4994a9463d5539bc83c3",
    "title": "Across, over, above or through",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "94d2e52ea9ae47958622f5f71a1c1030",
            "title": "Across, Over, Above, Through",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I saw him climbing ………………… the wall.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "across",
                        "through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "See if you can jump ………………….. the stream.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "across",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We swam ………………….. the river.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "across"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We walked ………………….. the ice.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "across",
                        "through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The plane was flying …………………… England.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "across",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is a little cottage ……………….. the lake.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "above",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can you see the helicopter hovering …………………. the palace.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "across",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We walked ………………… .. the wood.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "across",
                        "through"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was wearing a coat …………………… his pyjamas.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Your daughter is well ………………… average in intelligence.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}